His name's jack.
他叫Jack
He's a soldier,and he protects me.
他是个士兵 他保护我
I didn't mean to get you mad.
我不想让你生气
Please?
求你了?
I'll be a good boy.
我会做个乖孩子的
Please let me out.
求你让我出去吧
Peter.
Peter
Katie.
Katie
I think peter's back.
我想Peter 回来了
Peter? Are you sure?
Peter? 你肯定吗?
I just got a new image.
我刚刚收到一段新视频
The screen name onthe sender is hugz.
发布者的网名叫Hugz
He just uploadedthis to me.
他传这个给我
We're sure it'sa new image?
能肯定是段新视频吗?
New image,same boy.
新视频 同一个男孩
Time and datestamped an hour ago.
时间日期显示发布于一小时以前
- Are communicatingdirectly with this hugz? - No.
- 你有没有直接和Hugz 交流? - 没有
I'm in a chat room. I was just fishing.
我在一个聊天室里 放诱饵
Put him up.
和他联系
Carl,I need to know wherethis chat room originated.
Carl 我需要知道这个聊天室的地址
People,listen up.
伙计们 听着
We have a boy we namedpeter a year ago.
一年以前我们有个叫做 Peter 的男孩
At the time,he was listedbetween 5 and 6 years old.
当时他5到6岁
I.M. Hugz "vn-ho."
给Hugz 发消息"vn-ho."
Very nice.How old.
非常不错 几岁了
Very.
非常感兴趣
Go to the site.
上这个网站
That clock iscounting down.
这个时钟正在倒计时
It's an auction clock.
这是个拍卖计时钟
He's gonna sell peter.
他要卖了 Peter
Give me aaron hotchnerat the B.A.U.
帮我接 行为研究所的Aaron Hotchnerat
40,000 imagesof child pornare posted every weekon the internet,
每周有40,000 部儿童色情片 发布在网络上
along with the appearanceof 20 new children.
其中会有20个新的孩子
The appetite for babies as youngas 4 months old has soared.
对于四岁大小的孩子 的兴趣飞速增长
Many of these childrenhave been kidnappedand sold into pedophile rings.
许多孩子被绑架 然后卖给那些有恋童癖的人
One year ago,the same boy appearedon several web sitesused by pedophiles.
一年以前 这个男孩 在几个恋童癖网站上出现过
He was a new face then.
当时他是个新面孔
After a massive huntled by our crimesagainst children unit,the boy disappeared.
在我们反针对儿童犯罪的追捕下 这个孩子消失了
Until tonight whenS.S.A.Cole telephoned us.
直到今晚S.S.A.Cole 打电话给我们
Katie cole?
Katie cole?
She was inthe B.A.U.,Right?
她以前也是行为研究所的 是吧?
One of the firstprofilers,clinical psychologist,brilliant.
法医学绘画高手 临床心理学家 十分聪明
She runs the crimesagainst childrenunit in maryland.
她在马里兰州管理 反针对儿童犯罪局
I always wantedto meet her.
我一直都想见她
Really? I heardshe's a bitch.
真的吗? 我听说她是个婊子
Nobody ever calledyou that,katie.
可没人这么叫过你Katie
Well,not to my face.
哦 不是当着我的面
The first timeI ever saw him,he appeared in aseries of photos.
我第一次见到他时 他出现在一系列照片中
I named him peteR.
我叫他Peter
Now he's beingauctioned offwhen that clockruns to zero.
现在 当时钟归零时 他就要被拍卖掉了
Auctioned.
被拍卖
His face isn't pixilated.
他的脸并没打上马赛克
'Cause the unsubis confidentthat we're notgoing to be ableto identify himin time.
因为这个不明人物相信 我们不能在限时里找到他
What aboutthe site itself?
网站本身如何?
Can't we justtrack its origin?
我们能追踪到它的地址吗?
It's routed through aproxy server in belarus.
它在白俄罗斯设了代理
Even if that governmentwas friendly,peter'd be gonebefore we finishedthe paperwork.
即使对方政府十分友好 Peter 也会在我们完成文书申请之前消失
We don't need to worryabout the paperwork.
我们不必担心文书申请
We have garcia.
我们有 Garcia
- Better get on that,will you? - Yes,sir.
- 去负责一下 好吗? - 遵命 长官
So,what happeneda year ago,katie?
那么一年前发生了什么事Katie?
We cross-referencedthe images of the boy.
我们前后对照了这个孩子的照片
We talked to knownoffenders nationwide.
我们与全国已知的罪犯谈过
We narrowed the locationdown to the easternunited states.
我们把范围缩小到美国东部
We had some suspects in,but the trail went cold.
我们有过一些嫌疑犯 但追踪后来搁置了
Until today.
直到今天
With all due respect,miss cole,how is this time goingto be any different?
Cole 小姐 冒昧的问一下 这次情况又有什么不同呢?
We havea starting point.
我们已经开了头
The location where the imagewas first discovered.
最初发现这些影像的地方
A chat room--hosted by an independentweb companyin cleveland,ohio.
是俄亥俄州克里夫兰市的 一个独立网络公司兴办的聊天室
And this time,I am bringing youall in with me.
还有这一次 有你们帮我
Theologiandietrich bonhoeffer said,"the test of the moralityof a societyis what it doesfor its children."
神学家Dietrich Bonhoeffer 说道 "为孩子们所做的一切应成为衡量社会道德的标尺"
Well,if it isn'tdr.Reid.
唷 这不是Reid 博士吗
Elle. Wow.
Elle 哇
- Nice haircut. - Thanks.Yeah...
- 发型不错 - 谢谢 是啊...
I likeyour haircut,too.
我也很喜欢你的发型
Is that a boys' regular?
那是男孩的发型吗?
Yeah,it is.
是的 是的
Wa--do you not like it?
哇--你喜欢吗?
It's totally you.
很合适你
So,you're,uh... ok?
好的 你...还好吗?
I didn't think youwere back till next week.
我以为你下星期才回来
Oh,um,I gota text message,so...
我收到一条短消息...
then it was a mistake.
那一定是搞错了
Is there a case?
有案子吗?
Not untilyou're healthy.
在你健康以前 没有
Yesterday I found myselflooking forward towatching a soap opera.
昨天我发现自己无聊到 在看肥皂剧
Which one?
哪一部?
Please,can you put meback to work,hotch?
求你了 让我回来工作好吗Hotch?
The doctor hasn'tcleared you forthe field.
医生还没证明你能回来工作
- Please,hotch. - You need more time.
- 求你了Hotch - 你需要更多时间
I've been outfor 4 months.
我不工作已经四个月了
What I need is togo back to work.
我所要的就是回来工作
We're goingto cleveland.
我们要去克里夫兰
Reid's going tothe crimes againstchildren division. Go with him.
Reid 要去反针对儿童犯罪的组织 和他一起去吧
- But I can-- - or go home.
- 但我可以-- - 或者回家
I'm all yours,dr.Reid.
我全听你的 Reid博士
The image was uploaded toone of our C.A.C.Undercoversfishing in a chat room.
录像被传给了我们反儿童犯罪部门 设在聊天室里的一个鱼饵
We try to monitoras many of them as we can,
我们尽量多多监控那些人
pretending tobe children,pedophiles,whatever works on that site.
在我们假装儿童 恋童癖者 或者其他人
Did you run forensiclinguisticson the chat log?
你们有没有使用法庭语言学?
There might besomething to hugz'speech patterns.
上面可能有Hugz 的说话模式
It doesn't really work thatway with internet talk.
网络聊天并不是那么回事
Fear of flying?
害怕飞行?
Lengthy,deep-rootedissues of control?
长久以来根深蒂固的控制欲问题?
I--think better on my feet.
我-- 还是比较相信我的双脚
Most of the talkis abbreviated text--
大多数谈话都用的是缩写--
L.O.L.,Laughing out loud. I.M.H.O.,,In my humble opinion.F.T.F.--
L.O.L.哈哈大笑 I.M.H.O.据我所知 F.T.F.--
- face to face. - Right.
- 面对面 - 正确
Uh,pedophilescan be dividedinto two categories...
恋童癖者可分为两类...
situationaland preferential.
随意型和偏好型
Situational offendersrarely seek out children,
随意型罪犯很少主动出击寻找孩子们
but they'll take advantageof a situation whenpresented with it,
但是常利用环境提供的便利机会
whereas preferential offendersactively target childrenby age group,hair color...
而偏好型的则会主动选择 孩子的年龄段 头发的颜色
they'll seek out jobs whichgive them as much accessto children as possible.
他们会尽可能寻找那些 能更多接近孩子们的工作
The often trawl aroundresidential neighborhoods,hijacking homewireless systems
他们经常在住宅区附近下手 劫持家庭无线网络
and communicatingwith childrenoften outside the veryhouse the child is in.
然后就在孩子家门外和他聊天
Or they'll simply usea wireless coffee shopto find,locate,and arrange a meeting.
或者他们使用咖啡店的无线网络 去寻找 锁定目标 安排会面
And it's growing.
这种情况正在怎张
It's growing as fastas the internet.
与网络的普及一样与日俱增
They're gettingsmarter and smarter,
他们变得越来越狡猾
and all the securityin the worldcan't stop them fromcoming through our doors.
所有的安全措施都没法 防止他们找上门
Hell,the monsters arealready in our homes.
这该死的怪物已经进了我们家的门了
If he's had this kidfor a year,it makeshim preferential.
如果他关押了这个孩子一年 他就是偏好型的
Definitely.
没错
So,then why ishe selling him?
那么他们为什么要卖了他?
Maybe,uh... maybehe's losing interest.
也许 嗯... 也许因为失去兴趣了
Peter's maybe gettingtoo old,too tall.
Peter现在可能岁数大了 个子高了
Preferential offendersare very specificabout their preferences.
偏好型攻击者往往有 非常确定的偏好
And if he can't sell him?
那如果他卖不出去呢?
He isn't going tojust let him go.
他不会让他就这么走的
Hotch?
Hotch?
Yeah?
在?
Yeah,I was thinking,shouldn't we releasepeter's picture to the media?
我在考虑 我们是不是要把Peter的照片公之于众?
No.No,no.
不行 绝对不行
If this unsub thinksthat we're on to him,he may make a run for itand dispose of the boy.
如果这个不明人物觉得我们在找他 他可能就跑了 丢弃那个孩子了
Shouldn't we assumehe does know?
我们难道不应该假设他知道吗?
As I said,we interceptedthis image as part ofan undercover operation.
就像我所说的一样 我们是通过秘密操作截取图像的
These predators havea fairly closed society.
这些捕猎者有相当封闭的生活环境
The way they run thesesites gives them theexpectation of anonymity.
他们经营这些网站的方法 满足了他们匿名的需要
Right.
好的
Have reid and ellecheck the live feed.
Reid 和Elle 去检查现场录像了
Not just the boy,but everythingaround him--the room.
并不仅仅是这个孩子 还有房间里的所有物品
See if wemissed anything.
看看我们是不是遗漏什么
- Ok. - Yeah.
- 好的 - 是
Amanda gilroy.
Amanda Gilroy
You're the B.A.U.?
你们是行为研究所的吧?
I'm spender reedand this isagent greenaway.
我是Spender Reed 这是Greenaway探员
You're the agentwho had contact withthe image of peter.
你就是找到Peter 影像的探员吧
This time. A year ago,it was katie who firstidentified him.
这次是 一年前 是Katie 首先发现他的
- You call her katie? - Everyone does.
- 你叫她Katie? - 人人如此
She hatesto be called agent cole.
她很讨厌被叫成Cole探员
Make yourselves at home.
请随便
We just got yourwarrants approved.
我们刚刚拿到了搜查令
Katie and your team areabout to pay a visit tothe chat room vendor.
Katie 和你们组要去 拜访一下聊天室的经营者了
Yeah. Well,yeah.
是的 哦
We went overthe probability.
我们会再检验可能性
That's fine.
不错
Yeah.
是的
Yeah,one of our main onlinelisting sites is down,but we should beback online--fbi.
我们一个主要的分类网站瘫痪了 但我们会再修好--联邦调查局
We have a warrantto search these premises.
我们有搜查令搜查这件屋子
Stop what you're doingright now.
停下你们手头的活
I'm sorry. I gotta go.
很抱歉 我得挂了
Can somebody tell mewho owns this place? Ahem.
- 有没有人能告诉我谁管这个地方? - 嗯
That'd be me.
是我
I want access to yourchat room database.
我需要进入你聊天室数据库
It looks like thewalls are padded.
看上去墙被填充过了
- And the dimensionsare strange. - Strange?
- 大小很奇怪 - 奇怪?
- It looks like a hall,but smaller. - A basement?
- 看上区去像中厅但更小一点 - 地下室?
I don'tthink so.
我觉得不是
Katie just got us accessto the originalchat room's database.
Katie 刚刚进入了聊天室数据库
It's coming through now.
正在传过来
Must be thousandsof screen names there.
一定有成千上万的网名
All encrypted.
都设了密
Yeah,but we're onlyconcerned about one.
但我们只关心其中一个
Hugz.
Hugz
This is so typical.
这真有代表性
You feds just can'thelp yourselves.
你们这些联邦调查局的就是没事做
You gotta pollutethe truest form of freeexpression ever invented.
你们会破坏建立起的 自由言论模式
Agent find a chatroomof your choice.
Morgan 探员来找出你喜欢的聊天室
Your name is susie. You're 12 years old.
你叫Susie 今年12 岁
- What are you doing? - Fishing.
- 你在干什么? - 下饵
You know,I've got rights,and so do my clients.
你知道 我有我的权力 我的客户们也是
That's the soundof pedophiles lookingto hook up witha 12 year old girlnamed suzy.
这就是那些想要认识一个12岁叫做Suzy 的小女孩的恋童癖者的声音
You let them runeverything throughssl connectionsfrom proxy serversin offshore countries.
你让他们使用SSL加密连接的 海外代理服务器
So they can't be identified?
所以他们不能被定位?
Not in 12 1/2 hours.
没有12 个半小时不行
Hey,I'm justa middleman here,ok?
嘿 我只是个中间人 好吗?
What can I do?
我能做什么?
There's a little boy forsale on one of your sites.
在你的一个网站上正有个小男孩被出售
"What can I do"just isn't good enough.
"我能做什么" 还远远不够
Cole was right.
Cole 说得没错
Hugz routed throughan offshore proxy.
Hugz 连了一个海外的代理服务器
So we have no wayof tracking him?
所以我们没办法找到他?
Not if you only track himwith his address.
如果你单单追踪他的地址 不行
What else do we have?
我们还有什么?
He used a basicencryption programto hide hispayment method.
他用了一个很基础的加密程序 隐藏自己的付费方式
And as you know,I'm anything but basic.
而你知道 我可是专业人士
Ah,gotta lovethe money traila credit card leaves.
啊 真喜欢通过钱追踪信用卡
Well,well,well. Graham rose,15 hauser lane,rimond,va.
哦 哦Graham Rose Hauser街15号 Richmond 弗吉尼亚
Check this out,jj.
JJ 看看这个
He used the same cardto pay for a web domain.
他在网上也是用同一张卡 为域名付帐
Oh,my god.
哦 上帝啊!
Gideon,we just foundanother child being held.
Gideon 我们刚刚 又找到一个被绑架的孩子
Fbi!
联邦调查局!
You're a bad boy.
你真是个坏孩子
You needed to be tied up,didn't you?
你需要被绑起来 是吧?
Let me see you struggle.
让我看看你挣扎的样子
Clear! ********
安全! 行动
Fbi!
联邦调查局!
What are you doing?
你们在干什么?
Where is he?
他人呢?
Where is who?
谁啊?
- It's ok. - You're safe now.
- 没事了 - 你现在安全了
Safe?
安全?
- What's your name? - Kevin.
- 你叫什么? - Kevin
The man who didthis to you. Is he still here?
这样对待你的人 他在哪里?
It's my house.
这是我家
Graham rose is theowner of this house. Where is he?
Graham Rose 是这间屋子的主人 他人呢?
No,no! Don't touch that.
不 不! 别碰
Back up.
后退
- Where is he? - He's gone.
- 他人呢? - 他走了
What do you mean,gone? He's just gone,ok?
- 你指什么 走了? - 他刚刚走了 行了吧?
- Graham roseis your father? - Yeah,sure.
- Graham Rse 是你父亲? - 是的 当然
You can call him that.
你可以这么说
I just call him a bastard.
我叫他混蛋
You scared?
你害怕吗?
You think dad'smad at us?
你觉得爸爸会生我们的气吗?
The father's been in jailfor the last 8 months.
前8个月Kevin 的父亲在坐牢
In that time,kevin'sbeen selling the onlything he's got,which is himself.
那时候Kevin 就出卖他唯一的东西 他自己
Just likea street hustler.
就像个男妓
Only now the streetis the internet.
只不过现在马路成了网络
And his client basespans the globe.
而且他的客户遍布全球
Well,this kid definitelyuploaded peter's videoto the chat room,'cause it's stillon his computer.
是这个孩子上传了Peter 的录像 因为现在还在他的电脑里
Yeah,but notthe live feed.
但并不是现场直播的
He say how he gothold of the video?
他说他是怎么得到那段录像的?
He said it came fromone of his clients.
他说来自于他的一个客户
It was a shared file.
是个共享文件
They'd gone aroundthese chat groups.
在聊天群里流传
It's possible.
很有可能
Buyers and sellers routine.
买卖双方都依照惯例
They trade files becausethe act in itselfis an illegal act,which proves they'renot the police.
他们非法交流文件 由此证明他们不是警察
I'll see what elsewe can find out.
我去看看还能找到什么
Kid,the boy whose videoyou've been sending aroundto all the chat rooms,
孩子 那个你上传到网上 那段录像里的孩子
he's gonna be sold fromone pedophile to another.
就要被在恋童癖者间卖来卖去了
Boo-hoo.
唔 好可怜啊
These are dummy logs.
这些日志是假的
What's the passwordto get me intothe real transcriptsof your sessions?
查看你真正记录的密码是多少?
You're the fbi. You figure it out.
你是联邦调查局的 你自己找吧
I know you don'tthink so,kevin,but we are tryingto help you here.
我知道你并不这么认为 Kevin 但我们是在这里帮助你
Help me? What I dois consensual.
帮我? 我所做的都是两厢情愿的
No one's getting hurt.
没人受害
Come on,kevin,what's the password?
得了吧Kevin 密码是什么?
Your birthday? Your favorite band?
生日? 喜欢的乐队?
Kevin,this is prostitution.
Kevin 这是卖淫
But I'm a minor.
但我还是个未成年人
I don't even reallyknow what I'm doing.
我连自己在做什么都不知道
Plus I never leavethis room,so no one,no one ever touches me.
更何况我从没离开过这个屋子 所以没人能碰我
Anymore.
不再那样了
Your father's been beatingyou since you can remember.
你父亲从你记事起 就开始打你
First it was when he wasdrunk on the weekend,then he was always drunk.
起初只是在周末他喝醉时动手 后来他开始酗酒
You never knew whyhe was hurting you...
你从不知道他为什么伤害你...
why he was so angry.
为什么他那么生气
At night you'd cryyourself to sleep,hoping someone wouldcome and save you.
夜晚你哭泣着入眠 希望有人来解救你
No one ever came.
但从没有人出现
You have the chanceto be the one whosaves someone,kevin.
你现在有机会去解救别人Kevin
You can be the onewho answers him,the one who stopshis pain.
你可以成为回应他的人 解脱他的痛苦的人
You can't getto your father,but you can getto the guy who'shurting this boy.
你不能找到你父亲 但你可以找到伤害这个孩子的人
Move.
走开
This backs upall my transcripts.
这个备份了我所有的聊天记录
The screen name of the guy whosent me the file is mehtevas.
给我发送这个文件的人 网名叫做Mehtevas
Can you hear me?
你能听见我吗?
Can I get out anytime soon? Please?
我能快点离开这里吗? 求你了?
He's got food and water,a toilet and some toys.
他有吃的喝的 厕所和一些玩具
He never has toleave the room.
他不必走出房间
That's it! It's not a room.
是了! 这不是个房间
A room has a door.
房间得有门
Even a prisoncell has a door.
即使是牢房也有门
There are no windows,so he can't be seen,and the walls are paddedso he can't be heard.
没有窗户所以别人看不见他 墙壁被填充过了所以别人听不见他
The unsub's anticipatingbecoming a suspect.
不明人物希望成为嫌疑犯
So he's hidden the boy.
这么说他藏匿了孩子
If there are no doors,how did he get the boyin the room?
如果没有门 这个孩子是怎么进去的
It's like a shipin a bottle.
就像装在瓶子里的小船
He's built the roomaround the boy.
他在这个孩子周围建了个屋子
How long has mehtevasbeen a client of yours?
Mehtevas 成为你的顾客多久了?
Like,6 months.
大概 6 个月吧
Where is he located? He's a local.
- 他在什么地方? - 就是当地人
He's always askingto meet with me,but I don't do that.
他一直约我出去见面 但我不干
- Does he knowwhere you are? - Just the city.
- 他知道你在哪里吗? - 只知道我住城里
- How do you contact him? - He contacts me.
- 你怎么和他联系? - 是他联系我
Come on,kevin.
算了吧 Kevin
You don't just sitaround here waitingfor these guysto look you up.
你不会就干坐在这里 等着别人找上门
That's no wayto run a business.
这可不是做生意的办法
Right now you'rethe only person whocan help us find peter.
现在你是唯一一个能帮我们找到 Peter 的人
What do youwant me to do?
你想要我做什么?
Ask him fora face to face.
约他出来见面
No. No way.I don't do that.
不 没门 我不会这么做的
- I've never beenout of this room. - It'll be fine.
- 我从不离开这间屋子 - 会没事的
He won'tlay a finger on you.
他不会碰你一根手指头
We'll right there,kevin,the whole time.
我们会一直在你身边的Kevin
I promise you.
我向你保证
Won't he be suspiciousif I suddenly wantto meet with him?
我突然约他见面不会令他怀疑吗?
He's a need drivenoffender,kevin.
他是个应召型的罪犯 Kevin
What does that mean?
什么意思?
if you offer tomeet with him,he won't be ableto resist.
如果你主动提出见面 他无法抗拒
He can't help himself.
他情不自禁
You said that he firstappeared a year ago,right?
你说他第一次出现是在一年前 是吗?
But he wasin a normal room.
但当时他是在一间普通屋子里
The pictures didn'tlook like that.
照片看上去并不是这样
Here.
这里
So,something changed.
这么说有些东西改变了
A stressor for himto lock him away.
紧张性的刺激使他把小男孩藏了起来
Hey,guys.
嘿 伙计们
What is it?
是什么?
I'm not sure.
我不清楚
Wait,do you see howhe's looking off camera?
等等 你们看见他怎么看摄像头的吗?
Someone's telling himto do what he's doing.
有人告诉他怎么做
A bidder who must wantto see him wearing...
竞拍者想让他穿着...
wait a minute.
等等
That's a tadpole shirt.
那是蝌蚪衬衫
It's a wilderness group.
野外小组
Knot tying. Compass wielding.Boy stuff.
打结 手持指南针 男孩子们的游戏
Are you sure?
你确信?
I have 4 brothers,jj. They all hadthat shirt.
我有四个弟弟JJ 他们都有那件衬衫
Is that numberson his sleeve?
他袖口上是不是有数字?
Wait,wait,enhance it.
等等 放大放大
Capture that imagewhen he turns.
他转身时 抓张图
The badge is torn.
标志磨损了
It's like,4 numbers. What is that?
看起来有4个数字 那是什么?
3,something,something,6?
3 什么什么6?
That's a unit number. 4 digits endingwith a 6.
是个小组号 以6结尾的4位数
999 possiblecombinations.
999 种可能的排列组合
But a unit number wouldbe registered,right?
但是小组号会被注册是吧?
Already on it,kid.
已经开始查了 孩子
- Of course you are. - I rule.
- 那是 - 这就是我的规矩
They're headingto alexandria.
他们正在找Alexandria
They want us to lookup this addressand tell themwhat's there.
他们想让我们查查地址 然后告诉他们什么在那
- Plowright. - Alexandria.
- Plowright - Alexandria
That location,it's right outside ofan elementary school.
那个地方就在一所小学外面
Where are you going?
你要去哪里?
We can be therein 30 minutes.
我们可以在30分钟内赶到那
- You're not allowedto go anywhere. - Don't even try it,reid.
- 你哪也不准去的 - 别这样Reid
Don't you lovethat sound?
你不喜欢这种声音吗?
Excuse me?
什么?
- Children. - Mehtevas?
- 孩子们的声音 - Mehtevas?
You seem nervous.
你看上去很紧张
Well,you aremehtevas,right?
你是Mehtevas 对吗?
My friends call me hayden.
我的朋友叫我Hayden
Hey,you're tallerin person.
嘿 你长得很高啊
What's the matter? Did I say something wrong?
怎么了? 我说错什么了吗?
Hugz? Kevin?
Hugz? Kevin?
Fbi! Turn around!
FBI! 转身!
- Agent morgan. - I didn't do anything.
- Morgan探员 - 我什么都没做
Agent morgan,take it easy. Take it easy.
Morgan探员 放轻松 放轻松
We need his cooperation.
我们需要他的合作
We just want to ask youa few questions.
我们只要问你几个问题
Here's a question.What's the principalof a schooldoing hooking up witha 14 year old boy?
首先是 一个学校校长和 一个14岁的男孩约会干嘛?
Let's go.********
我们走 带走
Katie,social servicesis picking up kevinat the alexandriafield office.
Katie 社会服务人员把Kevin 从Alexandria地区办公室带走了
I'm going to gowith him.
我要和他一起走
I'll be backas soon as I can.
我会尽快回来的
- Are you ok? - Yeah.I,uh...
- 没事吧? - 恩 我 恩...
yeah.
没事
Hotch. You already got him?
Hotch 已经抓到他了?
I told you to stayout of the field.
我告诉过你不要参加现场行动
Yeah,I know. But reid said thatyou wanted us here.
对 我知道 但Reid说你要我们过来的
- No,I didn'T. - Yes,you did.
- 没 我没说 - 你说了的
- I'm sure you didn't,reid. - Thanks.
- 我知道你没 Reid - 谢谢
The school district hasgiven us permission tosearch rawlings' office.
学校方面已经允许我们 去搜查Rawlings的办公室了
I'm on it.*********
我就去 干的好
Principal of a school.
学校校长
As much access tochildren as possible.
拥有最多接近孩子的机会
Growing up guidefor parents.
家长们的楷模
He's got a library ofchild psychology.
好多儿童心理学的藏书
He's got adoctorate in it.
有一个这方面的博士学位
Well prepared pedophile.
天生的恋童癖者
- Elle,you noticeanything missing? - Computer.
- Elle 发现少了什么东西吗? - 电脑
Family man,so,if he does have peter,he's not keeping him at home.
居家男人 那么如果他真的关着Peter的话 不会藏在家里的
Elle,this one's locked.
Elle 这个锁了
Hey,move.
嘿 我来
Did they teach youthat in fbi school?
FBI学校教会了你这个?
No,they taught methat in brooklyn.
不 我在布鲁克林学的
I wish you would informme what exactly I'mbeing charged with.
我希望你们能告诉我到底 因什么罪名被起诉
Anything I canpossibly stick to you.
任何我能抓住的把柄
I haven't done anything.
我什么也没做
You're an educatedman,mr.Rawlings.
你受过良好的教育 Rawlings先生
You know you'rein trouble here.
你知道你有麻烦了
I believe I just walkedoutside my school.
我只不过是在我学校外面逛一圈而已
Is that a crime now?
那也算犯罪?
You knowwhere he is?
你知道他在哪里?
How could anyonehurt something so...
谁忍心伤害一个这么...
pure?
纯真?
You sent thisimage to kevin.
你发了这张照片给Kevin
Well,that was wrongof me,I know,but I was so shocked.
那个 是我不好 我知道 可我震惊极了
I wanted to try to savethis poor boy.
我想要救这个可怜的孩子
I thought hugz--kevin--might know him.
我以为Hugz--Kevin--也许认识他
That's why I sent himthe link to the website,see if he knew.
所以我才把那个网站的链接发给他 看看他认不认识那孩子
Please. You weretrying to save him?
得了吧 你是想救他?
Help search his office.
去帮着搜他办公室
I got this.
我来处理这个
How were you goingto save peter?
你准备怎么救Peter?
Peter? Is that his name?Peter?
Peter? 他的名字吗? 他叫Peter?
I wanted to save themboth.
我想救他们两个的
Kevin,too.
还有Kevin
Sit down.
坐下
Tell me we gotsomething we can nailthe son of a bitch on.
告诉我我们找到了 可以抓住那个杂种的东西
Not unless we canbreak the passwordon this guy'scomputer.
除非能破解他计算机的密码
- Call garcia. - Take too long.
- 打给Garcia - 那要很长时间
Come on,genius.
那就加把劲 天才
Do somethinggenius-like.
做点天才般的事情
If this guy doeshave child pornographyon his computerand we type inthe wrong password,it could triggera virus that wipesthe entire hard drive.
如果这家伙电脑里真的有儿童色情片的话 我们输错密码可能会启动病毒 而把硬盘上的一切东西都销毁
What's he saying out there?
他在那儿说些什么?
He's a preferentialpedophilewho claims he'strying to save theM.
这个恋童癖说他要救那两个孩子
Save them. Save--
救他们 救--
Mehtevas.
Mehtevas
Can you getany closer?
能再近点吗?
I can,but it'll distortthe image even more.
能 但图片会歪曲地更厉害
There,see,the edgeof his badge,it looks like itsays "mount" something.
那里 看 他徽章的边缘 好象写着"mount"什么的
Ok.
好
There are 4 unitdesignations,allstarting with mount.
有四个队名是以“mount”开头的
Mount clements,minnesota,2346.
Mount Clement 明尼苏达 2346号
Mount vernon,new york,2436.
Mount Vernon 纽约 2436号
Mount pleasant,virginia,3446. That's it,right?
Mount Pleasant 弗吉尼亚 3446号 就这样吗?
Yeah. Yeah,yeah,good one.
对 对 对 干的好
Mr.Rawlings,have a seat.
Rawlings先生 请坐
Your laptop.
你的手提电脑
Yeah,it's morgan.
对 是Morgan
Ok,hold on,garcia. Hold on.
好 别挂 Garcia 等等
It's,uh,research. I'm writing a book.
它是 呃 一项研究 我正在写一本书
Sit down.
坐下
I swear to you thisis all just research.
我发誓这些东西都是为了研究
It's not research.
这不是研究
It's 100 years in afederal penitentiary.
这是联邦监狱里的100年刑期
I'd like to make a deal.
我想做个交易
No deals.
没有交易
All you have is a very,verysmall amount of good will.
你所拥有的只是很小很小的良好愿望
Tell me about peter.
谈谈Peter
I was contacted by theman who was holding him.
是那个拥有他的人联系的我
I didn't search outthis boy.
我没要去特地找这个孩子
- I didn't go lookingfor this. - Give me a name.
- 我没去找这些 - 给我名字
Well,I only knowthe screen name.
那个 我只知道网名
It's manchild.
是Manchild
Did you bid on peter?
你给Peter出了价吗?
How much?
多少钱?
$8,000.
8,000美元
But it was onlyin order to save him.
但那只是为了救他
You the high bidder?
你出的价最多?
I--I think so,yes.
我--我想是的
I was,anyway.
至少曾经是
I was supposed to goback onlineand contact himon his web siteand get the address.
我本应该上网联系他然后得到地址的
So you can inspectthe merchandise?
这么说 你是可以去验货的?
Look,this child isbeing auctioned off,and I am tryingto save him.
听着 这个孩子被拍卖了 而我想去救他
Trying to save him.
想救他
He'd have given you a code. What is it?
他给了你一个密码 是什么?
Come on.
行行好
I have a family. I have childrenof my own.
我有家庭 我有自己的孩子
I love children.I would never harm them.
我爱孩子 我永远不会伤害孩子
In your pursuitto save them,you think you could haveavoided having sex with them?
在你救他们的过程中 你觉得你能 避免和他们发生性关系吗?
Mr.Rawlings.
Rawlings先生
The code.
密码
Butterfly.
蝴蝶
Dad?
爸爸?
When can I come out?
我什么时候能出来?
I'm being a good boy.
我是个乖孩子
- In live breaking news... - shut up...
- 特大新闻现场... - 闭嘴...
The fbi's crimescontrol unit and localauthorities have arrestedmark twain elementary schoolprincipal
FBI犯罪控制组和当地警方今天共同逮捕了 马克吐温小学的校长Hayden Rawlings
hayden rawlings today in what sources sayis a sting operationtargeting what may be
据说牵涉到
oneof the largest pedophile ringsthis country has ever seen.
国内最大的一个虐童网络
Both agencies have declinedto comment on the arrestat this time,or give any details of the case,
现在探员不愿意就逮捕行动 或案件具体内容作任何透露
but it is rumored to beconnected to the investigationof a child pornography ring.
但传言说和一个儿童色情网站有关
Experts in law enforcementknow that the explosionof social networking sites
法律界专家称网络已成为最佳的
- on the internetare a favorite huntinggrounds... - Hello,agent cole.
- 寻找目标的途径... - 你好 Cole探员
- What happened? - I don't know.
- 发生了什么? - 我不知道
He broke contact.
他断开了连接
- What happened? - The entire feedjust went dark.
- 怎么了? - 忽然什么都没了
Get Hotch on the phone.
让Hotch接电话
We got reporters outsideof the schools.
学校外面都是记者
This thing isall over the news.
到处都已经在播这条新闻了
My god,that's why the sitewent down. He knows.
天哪 所以网站没了 他知道了
She's sure aboutthis,right?
她对此很确定 对吗?
If garcia says thattadpoles shirt camefrom a unit inmount pleasant,then I gotta believe her.
如果garcia说那件蝌蚪衫是 Mount Pleasant的 我相信
She better be.Mount pleasantis 60 miles awayand there's onlytwo hours left onthe auction clock.
最好是 离Mount pleasantis还有60英里 而拍卖只剩下2小时了
Maybe.
也许吧
If the unsubknows we're on to him,he may movethat clock up.
如果那人知道我们正赶去那里 他会缩短拍卖时间的
Think this guy'sgonna panic?
你们认为这家伙会惊慌失措吗?
I don't know. Depends on hiscomfort level.
我不知道 那要看他的承受能力了
Maybe getting closeto auction time,he can wait it out.
也许接近拍卖结束时间 他会等下去的
I know one thing: Ican't lose peter again.
我只知道一件事情:我不能再失去Peter了
Well,let's justhope jj bought ussome time.
那就希望JJ能多给我们争取点时间吧
Mary,I need a favor.
Mary 我要你帮个忙
It's absolutelyall right that youbroadcast this.
你这么广播完全没问题
We have to bluffthis kid's captorinto believing we arein another locale.
我们要让抓这孩子的人以为我们在别地
It will buy us time.
那可以让我们多些时间
This kid's lifedepends on it. Ok,this is a lie.
这孩子的人生就靠这个了 对 就说个谎
Say the crimesagainst children unitis searching fora boy being heldcaptive in virginia.
说反针对儿童犯罪小组 正在弗吉尼亚搜索他的下落
He's approximately4 feet tall,he has brown hair.
大约4英尺高 棕色头发
We need you to get thison the air immediately.
我们需要你立刻播报
Thank you.
谢谢
The fbi has informed usthat they are looking fora missing 7 year old child.
FBI通知我们他们正在找一个 失踪的7岁大的孩子
This child is believedto be somewhere withinalexandria right now.
这个孩子可能现在就在Alexandria
A door to door searchis being coordinatedby the members of the crimesagainst children unit.
反针对儿童犯罪小组正在 一户户搜查该儿童下落
The boy is described asapproximately 3 feet tallwith sandy brown hair.
据描述该儿童3英尺高浅棕色头发
Jj,it's back.
JJ 他回来了
Uh,we got itback up,hotch.
恩 我们把他骗回来了 Hotch
We got an hour tillthe auction closes.
离拍卖结束还有一个小时
The site went dark fora few minutes and thencame back online.
这个网站关闭了几分钟 然后又上线了
So he believes the storyjj fed to the media.
这么说他相信了JJ对媒体说的那些话
But we've only gotan hour left.
但我们只有一个小时了
RighT.
没错
Tadpoles areaffiliated with a church.
蝌蚪的图案和一所教堂有关
When we getto mount pleasant,elle and morganshould go to the church.
我们到Mount Pleasant时 Elle和Morgan应去下教堂
We'll take the school.
我们去学校
Peter may beregistered there.
Peter可能在那里有登记
That sounds good.
听上去不错
I gave up on him.
我曾放弃了他
A year ago,I gave upon looking for him.
一年前 我不再对他抱希望
There were so manyother kids.
还有那么多别的孩子
Katie,I'm sure youdid what you could.
Katie 我肯定你做了你该做的
You ever ask yourselfhow you make a decisionlike that?
你问过你自己怎么做这样的决定吗?
How we come tothe conclusionthat it's time to moveon to the next kid.
什么时候我们能说该去关注下一个孩子了
How do you give yourselfthat kind of permission?
你怎么能允许你自己这样呢?
What's happened tothat boy in the year istopped looking for him?
我不再寻找那孩子的一年里 他身上发生了什么?
Recognize him?
认出他了?
Can't say that I do.
不能肯定
But you're certainthat the shirt camefrom this unit ofthe tadpoles,right?
但你认出了那衣服上的蝌蚪图案 是这个小队的 对吗?
It disbanded6 months ago,before i took overthe congregation.
这是6个月前解散的 就在我接管这个教会前
Why?
为什么?
I was told therewasn't enough interest.
因为我听说并没有人太感兴趣
Only a few boysparticipated.
只有几个孩子参加了
Do you have the recordsof those who did participate?
你有记录那些孩子是谁吗?
How could anyonedo this to a child?
怎么有人会这样对待一个孩子?
We need to find this boy.
我们要找到这个孩子
The records.
需要记录
I'm sorry.
很抱歉
I don't think so.
我想没有
Wait.
等等
There may be a photoof the tadpoles.
集会可能留下了点照片
This boy's ina terrible state.
这孩子的状况很不好
But do yourecognize him? Please look carefully.
你能认出他来吗? 请看仔细
You said his appearancemay have been altered?
你说他的样子可能变了?
First or secondgrade student.
一二年级的学生
Let me check my records.
让我看看记录
This may be whatyou're looking for.
这个可能就是你们要找的
Yeah,that's himright there.
对 就是他
Is there a name,address,anything?
有名字 地址 或是别的什么吗?
As I said,there areno records left.
就像我说的 没有任何记录
The church was run prettysloppily until I took over.
我接管之前教堂一直都缺乏管理
Let me see that.
让我看看那个
His name's charlie.
他叫Charlie
This is everyonewho registered forthe second grade.
这是二年级的所有注册学生
That's a lotof names.
有很多名字
What about the kidswho didn't register?
那没注册的孩子呢?
Excuse me?
什么?
Were there anyfirst graderswho didn't registerfor second grade?
有没有一年级的孩子 而没有注册二年级的?
I imagine therewere some transfers.
我想有几个转校的吧
Yes. Yes,therewere two transfers.
对 对 有两个转校生
Ashley watersand charlie sparks.
Ashley Waters和Charlie Sparks
Charlie sparks.
Charlie Sparks
Does it say wherecharlie's records went?
关于Charlie有没有记录去了哪里?
His father pickedthem up himself.
他父亲亲自来接走的
Can you describethe father?
能描述一下他父亲吗?
Oh,dear,no. I'd have no idea.
哦 我的天 不 完全没印象了
- Thank you. - The end of the school yearhere is so very hectic.
- 谢谢 - 去年最后在学校里有很严重的肺病
We have children from--
我们有孩子--
the name the schoolhas is charlie sparks.
学校里那孩子的名字是Charlie Sparks
No sparks in any ofthe phone directories.
电话本里没有任何姓Sparks的
Garcia can't even finda sparks within 100 milesfor the last 10 years.
Garcia甚至在近10年方圆100英里 都找不出一个来
Probably not hisreal name anyway.
也许不是他的真名
The school said hemay have moved away.
学校说他可能搬走了
Then we startover again.
那我们又得重新来了
We don't havea lot of time left.
没多少时间了
Guys,maybe we're lookingat this the wrong way.
伙计们 也许我们找错了方向
What do you mean?
什么意思?
The behavior,it's odd,right?
他的行为 是很古怪的 对吧?
The unsub apparentlylisted this kid in schooland the tadpolesuntil about a year ago.
那人一年前还让他的孩子去学校 以及参加集会
At that point he hadpictures of him onlinein a regular looking room.
那时只是把关在一个正常房间里的 孩子的图象发上网
But now he's ina prison-like roomwith no windows,no doors,completely hidden.
而现在 孩子却被关在像监狱一样 没门没窗完全封闭的房间里
Preferential pedophilesdon't change overnight.
先天的恋童癖不会一夜之间改变
So,what happened a yearago to make him changehis behavior so much?
那么一年前发生了什么使他这样做?
Fear.
恐惧
Katie almost caught him.
Katie几乎就抓住他了
You probablytalked to him.
你也许还和他谈过
The unsub'sin your records.
那人就在你的单子里
Guys,we justran out of time.
伙计们 我们快没时间了
I never reallyhad a good suspect.
我从来都没找到合适的嫌疑人
I only did somegeneral interviewswith child offenderson the east coast.
我只对东海岸一些有过 侵犯儿童记录的人做过常规询问
One of them wasthe right guy.
其中有一个就是要找的人
Amanda,hey.
Amanda 嘿
Uh,I need youto pull all ofthe original fileson peter's case.
呃 我要你把Peter案子所有的 原始文件调出来
Somewherein my office. Try my desk.
在我办公室里 看看我的桌子
I need the names ofeveryone I interviewed.
我要所有我询问过的人
Have her callpenelope garciaat the B.A.U.
让她找行为研究所的 Penelope Garcia
She'll be able to tell usif we can cross any off.
她能告诉我们该排除什么
You got it? Thanks.
明白了? 谢谢
- You still there? - Yeah.
- 还在吗? - 对
Oh,oh,oh, Got it,got it,got it.
哦 哦 哦, 有了 有了 有了
Ok,uh,frank portwell,dob 11 april 1962.
好 恩 Frank Portwell 1962年4月11号出生
He's doing 12 yearsin westover prison.
他正在Westover监狱服12年刑
Martin devries,dob 20 november '70.
Martin Devries 1970年11月20号出生
Got a death certificatefor him. Shot on the streetlast january.
有他的死亡证明书 去年1月在街上被枪杀
All righT.
好的
Michael earlson,dob...
Michael Earlson 生于...60年1月16日
garcia,you're sure?
Garcia 你确定?
Ok,no.No,no. I got it all.I got it all.
好 不 不 不 我知道 都知道了
All right,thanks,baby. You're the best.
好的 谢谢 你是最棒的
All right,guys.Listen up. We might have something.
好了 伙计们 听着 我们可能发现了点东西
12 men were interviewed.
12个人接受了询问
8 are back in prison,one is dead.
8个在监狱中 1个死了
One lives in california,and two have lastknown addresses within10 minutes of us--a patrick forestand a michael earlson.
1个住加州 还有2个最后的地址离这里10分钟 一个叫Patrick Forestand 一个叫Michael Earlson
Patrick forest isn'tsmart enough to putthis all together.
Patrick Forest没那么聪明搞这些
- What aboutmichael earlson? - Definitely.
- 那Michael Earlson呢? - 绝对是他
Where are you going?********. don't move!
你要去哪里? 别动!
Daddy!
爸爸!
it's okay,it's okay.
没事 没事了
you're save now. i got you,i got you.
你没事了 找到你了 找到了
where's daddy?
我爸爸在哪里?
I know.
我知道
Peter's real name is *********.
Peter的真名是Dustin Powers
*** adopted him in north new jersy when he was****
他在新泽西州北部收养的他 当时他一岁
sometimes it's the same as ****** punishment enough.
有时候任何惩罚都是不够的
jj chases his mother.
JJ追查到了他母亲
- she's on her way. - okay.
- 她正赶过来 - 很好
you know katie,no one has ever done the job you are doing as long as you are doing it.
知道吗Katie 只要你继续干下去 就没别人来做
I know.
我知道
maybe it's time to get out.
也许是时候该离开了
I don't know if I can anymore.
我不知道我还能不能坚持下去
I just can't thank you all enough.
我不知道要怎么谢你们
remember what I told you.
记住我告诉你的
here's ****** say hello but,
他不认识你，你可以问个好
does anything about being his mother that'll just scare and confuse him.
别说你是他母亲的任何话 那只能吓到他，让他困惑
okay.
好的
It's gonna be a long process.
那将是个很长的过程
I'll have to ******
我明白
****** this way.
这边走
What's his name?
他叫什么?
His name's jack.
他叫Jack
He's a soldier. He protects me.
是个士兵 他保护我
It's nice tomeet you,jack.
很高兴认识你 Jack
My name is jackie.
我叫Jackie
- Really? - Really.
- 真的吗? - 真的
Can I see jack?
我能看看Jack吗?
be Careful.
小心点